{
    "subject": "resource/Freedom_Downtime",
    "predicate": "ontology/narrator",
    "object": "resource/Eric_Corley",
    "human_readable": "Eric Corley is the narrator of Freedom Downtime.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7491410970687866,
            "question": "Who narrates the book 'Freedom Downtime'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6539334058761597,
            "question": "What makes Eric Corley a good narrator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5096629858016968,
            "question": "Are there other books narrated by Eric Corley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5022091865539551,
            "question": "Is Eric Corley known for narrating books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4925518333911896,
            "question": "What is the name of the book narrated by Eric Corley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47374069690704346,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'Freedom Downtime'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3679417073726654,
            "question": "How popular is 'Freedom Downtime' among listeners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33102500438690186,
            "question": "What other works has Eric Corley been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3237568140029907,
            "question": "What genre is 'Freedom Downtime' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31228211522102356,
            "question": "Where can I find 'Freedom Downtime' to listen to it?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Corley is the narrator of Freedom Downtime.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5468_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'Freedom Downtime' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5468_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other works has Eric Corley been involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5468_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular is 'Freedom Downtime' among listeners?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5468_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5468_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention Eric Corley as a narrator for any film. Instead, they indicate that he directed and produced the documentary \"Freedom Downtime.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context suggesting that Eric Corley, also known as Emmanuel Goldstein, is the narrator of Freedom Downtime. The context only states that he directed and produced the film, but there is no mention of his role as a narrator.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that \"Freedom Downtime\" is a documentary film directed by Emmanuel Goldstein, and later identifies Eric Corley as Emmanuel Goldstein.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates that Freedom Downtime was a documentary film directed by Emmanuel Goldstein, who is Eric Gordon Corley under his pen name. There is no mention of Corley as the narrator of the film.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}